hello I had to go and do that this cuz
my kid does it or she got it from and
she does it every time there's a picture
taken of her I love it um it's very her
but I tried to start a different channel
like under just me and then I was gonna
post five minute videos daily five
minute videos of me live and if people
come on and it distracts me then I'm
gonna post the live video privately and
then turn it public afterwards so that I
can do it in one take without having to
feel like I need it to be perfect cuz
live is there's just a different level
I'm just getting this now so I'm guess
if we might not get to the zeitgeist
right I might have to change the title
in this one it's probably also would I
need to go in and change on things like
I have this topic and then I hit live
and everything changes but when I was in
school before brain tumors and brain
damaging and whatnot personality-wise I
just I'm a procrastinator and would
procrastinate studying and writing
essays and all this stuff into the last
minute so if there was an essay it was
supposed to be for like we had weeks to
do it I'm doing it now in the like
afternoon before it's due so therefore
I'm getting a C on it right like that's
not a good way to write a paper but I
did like consistently through university
that's what I did but if I was writing
an in-class essay I more or less had the
same amount of time to do it in and
would get an A on it because one I'd
perfected the writing an essay in two
hours any - I was gauged against other
people who write an essay and two hours
- no no for two weeks and in this story
I'm the one who's in the wrong like I'm
the one who left the other one but it
was like I liked in-class essays because
it was a different bar okay my grammar
spelling like it was just a different
part you didn't have to do the research
the same way and stuff and I guess it's
kind of like that with these live videos
like well if I do it live the bar is
that I don't have to cut out the almonds
in the oz in the blinking whereas if
it's a five-minute uploaded video then I
would so yes I'm going to
change the name of this one to that that
I'm gonna be doing daily five-minute
videos and then I'm gonna do two today
because that's fun